Hi, boss.
Driver sustained heavy lacerations
and head trauma
but believe it or not
they're saying he'll live.
Lucky.
Victim's Sharon Warwick, 23.
She went off of a balcony,
room 914.
Rigsby's up there right now
with the forensics team.
Now off the bruise on the cheek
and the ripped vest
we're thinking it's murder.
- Catering staff?
- Actually, she was a cast member.
Show's called "Torch".
It's a story about intersecting
lives and loves
in a New York night club
in the 1950s.
The event tonight
was a fund-raiser for the show.
Multiple witnesses say
the time of death is 8:01 p.m.
right when the performance
was set to begin.
- Well, what was she doing up there?
- We don't know yet.
She was I.D.'d
by Warren Dodge, the producer.
- He's in there with the director.
- All right.
Poor Sharon.
Tragedy. Absolute tragedy.
But you know what?
We're gonna regroup and we'll move
forward from this, Bran
better and stronger.
You'll see.
Warren, our star is in a cab blotto
our second lead is dead.
How do you propose
we do better and stronger?
- Bran, listen...
- Mr. Dodge?
- Yes?
- I'm Agent Lisbon.
I need to ask you
some questions.
Of course. Of course.
Can you give me just one minute?
Bran, we are going
to get "Torch" to Broadway.
We are, all right?
I'll take care of the investors.
Hanover is solid,
that's 50% of our money.
It's only the other investors
we have to worry about, all right?
Your job is to keep calm and reassure
the cast and crew, all right?
- Mr. Dodge.
- Yes?
- And you are?
- Bran McTavish, the director.
Did either of you actually
see Sharon Warwick fall?
- I was inside. The show was starting.
- And I arrived right after it happened.
Do you have any idea what
she was doing up in room 914?
Well, we were using that area
as a dressing room for this event.
She was supposed
to be down in the ballroom.
She was third cue.
- Third cue?
- Yeah.
We had, actors scattered about
dressed as hotel guests, workers, caterers.
It was Bran's idea
to start the show.
Yeah, a guest breaks out into song
then the bellboy, then the waitress.
That was Sharon.
She was supposed to be
in the ballroom.
You've both been really helpful.
If you wouldn't mind going up to the room
while we start the investigation
- I'd be grateful.
- Anything we can do.
Hey, Lisbon.
"Where the hell are you?"
"Don't tell me
you're at the hospital."
- I'm not at the hospital.
- "We caught a case."
"You're needed
at the crime scene."
I'll be there soon.
You're at the hospital,
aren't you?
You told me to tell you
I'm not at the hospital.
What do you want?
Make up your mind.
Get out of there.
If Jason Lennon wakes up
and if he talks
"and if he knows
Red John's identity"
"Agent Kirkland and Homeland Security
are perfectly capable of handling it."
I disagree.
You're playing with fire.
There are worse things to play with.
Oh, gotta go.
- Agent Kirkland.
- How did you get in?
- This wing is closed to visitors.
- My Aunt Daphne's in room 10.
Kidney failure.
Poor dear. Drinks like a fish.
You must be broken up about it.
Look at you. You're a mess.
We both know why you're here.
Although I find your need to talk to Lennon
now interesting.
You did stand by while
Lorelei Martins shot him.
How's he doing?
He'll live to talk to us.
And I'll let you know if he has
anything interesting to say.
You're always good
to talk to you, Patrick.
But I think you should go now
before we start disturbing the patients.
- This way, sir.
- Yeah. I'm going. That's my arm.
You have two of your own.
Thank you.
How did you get in here?
Who let you in?
Well, if I told you that,
I wouldn't be able to get in
when I come back, would I?
did anybody have access
to the suite besides Sharon?
This served as a sort of communal
dressing area for this event
so, everybody, really.
The whole cast plus myself,
Dodge, and, Sylvia.
Hey, have you spoken to Hanover?
I wanna make sure he hears
about this from us first.
Sylvia, you worry
about the other investors.
Let me deal with Hanover, all right?
This is Sylvia Clare, our publicist.
Sylvia, Agent Lisbon
is with the CBI.
- Who's Hanover?
- Our patron. Our main investor.
Oh, Jane, there you are.
- This is the...
- No need. I just caught up in the elevator.
Dodge, McTavish, and Clare
producer, director, publicist.
Was Sharon having any trouble
with the cast or crew?
No, no. Not at all.
We're a very happy family
here at "Torch."
Yes, of course.
That's exactly what a good publicist
should say, isn't it?
Where were you when
the victim fell, Ms. Clare?
Oh, I was in the ballroom.
Mr. Dodge, what made you wanna cast
Sharon Warwick as the second lead?
According to this, she doesn't
have much theater experience.
Her paragraph's very short.
Well, Sharon came out here
from New York
and she just knocked Bran out
with her audition.
And, I trust his judgment.
She's a natural dancer, big voice
quick learner, and she was hungry.
That's all you need.
Well, what was in it for her?
I mean, it's a revival in the sticks.
She was already
a well-known singer in New York.
She wanted to be a part
of something special.
Exactly. I mean, we're starting
out here in Sacramento
but "Torch" will be on Broadway
in six months.
And a Tony contender in nine.
Did the cast have much contact
with the locals?
I don't know. I don't...
I don't think so.
Oh, I wouldn't think
they'd have the time.
They would have been right
into rehearsals straightaway.
- Yeah. That's right.
- So, yeah.
So you think like me.
The killer is connected to your musical.
Any guesses?
No? Okay. Thanks.
I'm sorry. Who is that?
He's a consultant.
Thank you for your time.
The suspect pool is huge.
It's gonna be a nightmare.
Why start on such a pessimistic foot?
Why are you so glum?
I call you up, and you're
creeping around Lennon
getting into Kirkland's business.
Of course I'm glum.
- Oh, that.
- Yeah. That.
We look bad enough after
the whole Lorelei Martins mess.
Lennon is a direct link to Red John.
I need to talk to him.
You need to try and start following
the rules for a while.
And if you must break the rules
break them on your own time.
When am I not on my own time?
"Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Better than nothing"
"oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh"
"You're better than nothing,
Than nothing"
- "Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh"
- Grace.
It's so good to see you.
- Hi.
- How was L.A.?
I learned a lot of really great stuff but
I don't know how anybody lives there.
I'm really happy to be home.
- Well, welcome back to the grindstone.
- Yeah. What's with the music?
Our victim's a singer.
She was pushed out of a window.
It's kind of catchy, huh?
It was an Internet hit.
She comes out here to star
in a musical and gets killed.
Van Pelt! Welcome back.
Thanks, boss.
It's good to be back.
It's good to see you.
How we doing so far?
Good. Found out that Warwick
was actually a local.
Really? The people from the theater company
seemed to think she was from New York.
No, I spoke to a Polly Datch.
Said she was Warwick's foster mother
here in Sacramento.
She's on her way to CBI.
What about Warwick's timeline
the night of the murder?
I've spoken to about
half the cast so far.
Bad news is they were leaving the door
to that room unlocked for ease of access.
So anyone could have been in there
when she died?
Yeah. The good news is we got
a whole lot of video
and photos to work off.
So the cast left the room at around
a quarter of 8:00 to get into position.
Warwick was with them.
She leaves the ballroom at 7:52.
At 8:01, she hits the limo.
Was anyone else from production missing
during that period?
I can't tell just yet.
I'll keep digging.
Did anybody leave
in a hurry after she fell?
Yeah, one.
Deandra Sunderland, the star.
Now the rumor among the cast
is that she's got a drinking problem
so they think she's probably getting sauced
in one of the, hotel bars.
A fading diva with a drinking problem?
That's unusual.
Yeah. Check this out.
This is her leaving out the back door.
- Well, when was that?
- About half-hour after the murder.
What about the surveillance footage
from the hotel?
Cameras in the lobby and all the elevators.
It's being sent over.
What about the investor... Hanover?
Do you have anything on him?
Yeah, the cast had a lot to say
about him, too.
Apparently he can buy Delaware.
We also found his arrival in the party
footage the publicist sent over.
I looked him up on the Internet.
He's a currency trader,
and he likes the arts.
Hey, boss, Polly Datch,
victim's foster mom...
- wants to talk to you.
- All right.
Mrs. Datch?
I'm Agent Lisbon.
You were Sharon Warwick's
foster parent?
- Yes, ma'am.
- For how long?
Sharon came to live with me
when she was 12.
Never knew her biological parents.
I stay close with most of my kids
but Sharon was special.
That's the man you need to find...
- Billy Racine.
- Who is he?
No-good thug, that's who.
- Is he an ex-boyfriend?
- He was her one bad choice.
Had she been in contact with Racine
since you came back to town?
I'm sure of it.
And I think he assaulted her
a week ago.
You think?
I don't really know because
she wouldn't talk about it.
She brushed it off,
called it a botched mugging.
But I'm certain it was him.
Why else wouldn't she report it?
Had he been violent with her
in the past?
Sharon said no, but...
I know Billy Racine
is a violent man.
Sure.
Of course, Mr. Hanover.
Thank you for your time.
Finally found Hanover?
Yeah. He didn't see
the crash either
but he said he'd be
happy to talk to us
- when he gets back in town.
- Back in town?
He had to fly to an art opening.
A piece he just had to have.
- Rich people.
- What'd you get?
Lisbon got this
from the foster mom.
Name's Billy Racine.
Ex-boyfriend.
Foster mother thinks
he could have done it.
Guy's had a life.
Multiple assaults, extortion.
That name sounds familiar.
"Racine William."
He's on the list of people
who purchased tickets
to the show's fund-raiser.
What was he doing there?
I'll see if I can
track him down.
Thanks.
What were you doing
at the fund-raiser for "Torch"
- two nights ago?
- Supporting the arts.
Did you have any contact with
Sharon Warwick that evening?
If I did, what's it matter?
You two had quite the tempestuous
relationship
before she moved to New York.
Shouting matches.
You even put your fist through a wall.
Did you pick up where you left off
when she came back a month ago?
Don't even try to pin this on me.
I know what's happened,
and I didn't kill her.
Why should I believe you?
Because I would never
put my hands on that girl.
I loved her.
I think you loved her
maybe too much.
She rejected you
you didn't take "no" for an answer
you stalked her to the fund-raiser.
And when she rejected you again
your hands got the better of you.
- I went there to protect her.
- Protect her from what?
She got mugged last week.
Said she fought 'em off
and scratched one of them up
pretty good
but I could see
she was shook.
What does that have to do
with the fund-raiser?
Sharon thought someone
from the show set it up.
So when I heard
they were doing that party...
You went to find her attackers?
I was gonna tune some people up.
But Sharon said "be easy."
Said she'd handle it.
- Did she say who she suspected?
- She wouldn't say.
She was scared I was gonna do
something bad to 'em.
And she was right.
So you're telling me everything
was good between you two?
You've been talking to
that old foster lady, huh?
She never liked me.
You can't believe
what she says.
"Why do fools fall in love?"
Okay. One second. One second.
that's your cue, Deandra.
Tell me again...why am I helping
you audition replacements?
Well, because our investor performance
was rescheduled
and, we have to be ready.
So if we could try it one more time
that would be wonderful.
I don't think you really need me
for this, Bran, okay?
I'll be in my dressing room.
No problem!
Okay...
Mandy, Bridget, Howard
from where we left off.
One, two, three.
"Love is a losing game
Love can be a shame"
"I know of a fool you see"
"For that fool is me"
"Tell me why"
Sorry. Sorry. Wait.
This is a closed rehearsal.
Yeah. We're investigating a murder.
Well, you won't find any clues here.
Actually, we could learn a lot
from watching a rehearsal.
Oh, really?
Yes. The way a person sings
says a great deal about them.
For instance, Bridget,
you have a very sweet tone.
Thank you.
Yes, with nice shades
of pent-up anger and envy.
You hated Sharon on principle
yet you may come to replace her.
So obviously, you had very good
motive to want to kill her.
But I don't think you have
the stomach or the strength
to push someone off a balcony.
You, Mandy, on the other hand
are perfectly capable of murder.
You have a very strong instrument.
You could play Sharon's part.
But are you hungry enough to kill?
Do you have that kind of passion?
I don't know. Hmm?
Oh, don't even look at me.
Thank you.
Oh, please. Pitchy.
Very... pitchy
You done?
Yes. Well, that leaves you,
Mr. McTavish.
Vain. Controlling.
Neurotic. Egotistical.
Sleeping with...
at least two of your actors.
Are you a killer?
You know, I never did
catch your name.
Damn.
I was sure it was you.
Never mind. Name's Jane.
Nice to meet you all.
Break a leg.
Well, I thought
you sounded... great.
- He's upsetting the performers.
- I know. I know.
- He's gonna throw their performances off.
- Bran, I'll take care of it.
- All right.
- All right?
Mr. Jane.
Please. Your presence
isn't good for morale.
Everyone seems
to be handling it okay.
You've asked your questions.
Is it necessary that you remain?
We'll stay out of your way.
You'll hardly know we're here.
Pardon me. Okay,
so I've gotten confirmations
from all of our bigger investors.
They will all be
at the rescheduled preview.
Excellent. And, Hanover?
- Still need to double confirm.
- Good. Good.
- Busy, busy.
- Indeed.
If you'll excuse me,
I have to take this.
Sure.
Excuse me.
Sorry to bother you.
I was wondering if you knew
what jazz hands were?
Sure. It's the use of big hand movements
in choreography.
Why do you ask?
Oh, I just overheard the director
ranting about jazz hands
so I was curious to know
what got him so worked up.
Ranting how?
Well apparently, he hate,
hate, hates jazz hands.
And if he sees one jazzy little hand
that dancer is out of the show.
Oh. Good to know.
Thanks.
No worries. you might
wanna pass that on
to the girl that comes up
after you.
Break a leg.
Okay, Maggie, you're up.
So what exactly are we looking for
with these auditions?
We'll know when we see it.
- You like musicals?
- Oh, what's not to like?
Wow. They're so good.
How many more are there?
I'm not sure.
A troublemaker should reveal
herself very shortly.
No! No! No, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
What are you doing, Bridget?
Suddenly we were in
a cabaret bar in Idaho.
I thought you wanted
bigger hand movement.
What gave you that idea?
I'm sorry, but this,
might indirectly be my doing.
I told the first dancer
that the director
would fire anyone
that added big hand movements.
What?
And she, along with everyone
else who auditioned
made sure that the dancer
that came after them
didn't use the jazz hands
so that they didn't
lose their job...
until Bridget.
Mandy came before me.
You can't be serious.
Only a scheming
and conniving person
would so callously try
to get a fellow cast mate fired.
There's no telling how far
someone like you will go.
Is he telling the truth, Mandy?
What does it matter?
At least the hands distract away
from the dreadful
syncopation problem you have.
- You wanted me to fail?
- That's not hard.
You bitch.
- Rigsby?
- Okay.
I'm sorry. What did you just call me?
- Oh, I'm sorry...
- Get your hands off me!
You mind stepping in
and handling this?
Ladies, ladies, ladies...
I have an errand to run.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Okay, let's...
Help!
Okay.
I know you're only talking to me
to get information out of me
but it's been nice.
You make me smile.
Well, what's worth
more than a smile?
True enough.
Mr. Lennon is pretty much stable.
His blood volume is up
and the doctors could bring him
out of the coma
as early as tomorrow.
Thank you. That's very good to know.
What is all this about?
And why are the federal guys
so weird and creepy?
They are? How are they
weird and creepy?
Like they're not
what they seem.
Like one day they might
pull their faces off
and there'd be alien lizards
underneath, you know?
I know. Not impossible,
but very unlikely.
- I know. They just have that vibe.
- I understand.
Will you call me when they bring
Mr. Lennon out of his coma?
- Sure.
- Thank you. I appreciate that.
Interesting set of scratch marks.
What happened?
Cat.
Sharon Warwick fought back
against one of her attackers
when she was mugged.
Know anything about that?
You know they found D.N.A. samples
under Sharon's nails after the murder?
It's amazing how a little D.N.A.
can tie two people together.
Okay. The mugging, that was me.
I just wanted to scare her a little bit.
I didn't kill her.
Who was your accomplice?
A guy named Joey.
He's my partner
in salsa class.
And why did you want
to scare her?
Because she was just some girl
with an okay voice and no resume
and there she was headlining
with Deandra.
And that made you mad?
Second lead should have
been me, not Sharon.
So when she showed up
for the fund-raiser
ready to launch
a star-making turn
you snapped and you pushed her
off that balcony.
I told you I didn't kill her.
Well, you've already admitted
to organizing an assault.
Why is it so crazy to think
that you didn't decide
to finish the job?
Because I didn't
want her dead.
I just wanted her to leave.
If you're looking
for suspects
you might wanna check out
the star of the show.
Deandra Sunderland?
The queen of mean.
What makes you think Sunderland
could have killed Warwick?
Because the director wanted to
replace Deandra with Sharon.
Everybody knew it.
I mean she's too old to be
playing the ingenue, right?
Did you see Sunderland
the night of the murder?
No. She was nowhere to be found
when the overture began.
What about after the accident?
Not until rehearsal the next morning.
"Every time"
"We say goodbye'
"I die"
"A little"
"Every time"
"We say goodbye"
"I wonder why"
"A little"
Yes, Mr. Hanover. Excellent.
Yeah. Yes.
No, that sounds good.
Okay. Sounds good. Sure.
We'll see you very soon.
Thanks.
Sorry. How long
you gonna keep Mandy?
A while. That's what we do
when people break the law.
Okay, look, agent, I'm a pro.
I can spin this tragedy.
It can even add an air of fascination
to the production.
But if you arrest the cast
right before a performance
for the investors
that makes my job
rather difficult.
You see, I need my investors
to stay... invested.
Well, brace yourself
because now I need to talk
to Deandra Sunderland.
This is a nightmare.
"There's no love song finer'"
"But how strange"
"The change"
"From major to minor"
Miss Sunderland.
My apologies for interrupting.
We need to talk.
I'm rehearsing here.
I asked not to be disturbed.
This is important.
Where were you when Sharon Warwick
fell off the balcony?
I was in the ballroom.
All of our evidence
points to the contrary.
Everybody involved in the production
seems to think you were off drinking.
I think you might have been
with Sharon.
I think you found out that
McTavish was planning
on replacing you with her,
and you got mad.
He wanted Sharon
to replace me?
She was studying film
of all of your performances
and memorizing your lines.
You don't understand.
She would if you told her the truth.
You sing beautifully.
- How long have you been out there?
- Long enough.
You know, I kept wondering
what brought Sharon Warwick
back to Sacramento.
She left Sacramento
because she wanted something
and now she's back.
It's obviously connected
to "Torch"
but it couldn't be acclaim
she was looking for
'cause she got that
in New York City.
And then I heard you sing,
and it came to me.
What is it that every foster child
is looking for?
Lisbon, I'd like you to meet
Sharon Warwick's mother.
I was...
Very young when I had Sharon.
Her father was my director,
and he was married.
The hardest thing I ever did in my life
was giving her away.
When did she learn
she was your daughter?
She came to my dressing room
after the first day of rehearsals.
Must have been a shock.
I felt so happy seeing the person
that she had become.
So talented, so...
full of life.
Why did you keep it a secret?
Guilt. Shame.
Something else.
You're hiding
something else.
You're quite a clever policeman,
aren't you?
I have multiple sclerosis.
Diagnosed six months ago.
I'm sorry.
Symptoms of the disease
is what made people think
you were drinking.
Well, I've been sober
for 14 years.
Haven't touched a drop.
I heard the whispers
behind my back.
I thought it might be better to quit.
Sharon was so mad.
Already protective towards me.
She told me to be strong.
And you had an attack
right before the first performance,
didn't you?
You didn't have your medication.
Yes.
Sharon said she'd go up
to the suite and get it for you.
She was an incredible young woman.
That's why I can't quit
the show.
I have to go on with it...
to honor my child.
Morning.
- Morning.
We've been through all the photos, videos
and security footage.
Cross-indexed every guest, hotel worker
attendee, and person
connected to the play.
All their movements are
accounted for, except for him.
Berndt Hanover, the investor?
Yeah, here he is before the murder
getting into the elevator.
He goes to the floor
Sharon Warwick was killed on
and gets off, and that's
the last time we see him.
What do you mean?
How can that be?
I don't know.
He never gets back on the elevator
and he's never seen
leaving the building.
Okay, but how? Why?
How does he leave the building
without being seen?
If he waited until the hallway
was empty
he could've taken the stairs
down to the first floor.
Yeah, but how does he avoid
being seen after that?
It...it's not like he's a guy
who doesn't stand out.
True.
This is the room
the murder took place.
That's the balcony.
Doorway out here to the corridor.
Past the stairs,
down to the elevators.
This, if I recall, was a window
out to a fire escape.
Could he have gone down
a fire escape?
He's a big man.
I don't think he's that agile.
Then what?
Yes, it's a puzzle.
Why do you look so happy?
You have a way to solve
the puzzle?
Naturally.
Meet me at the theater.
This is good work.
Keep me informed
of your progress.
Why are you lurking
out there, Mr. Jane?
I need a favor.
Is this the type of favor where...
You would then owe me
a favor?
Actually, you already
owe me a favor
but I'll spot you another
if that pleases you.
What do you need?
I need you.
Okay, 15 minutes to curtain, people.
Let's pick it up, pick it up.
Hey.
Deandra, don't forget to wait
three bars in the first intro, okay?
Darling, I've been doing this
since before you learned
to wipe your own nose.
Worry about your own business.
Never direct. Never direct.
Ladies and gentlemen,
if you will kindly enter the theater
and take your seats, please.
Hey, Lisbon,
you at the theater yet?
Jane, where are you?
On my way.
Almost there.
You head backstage.
We'll see you in a minute.
We? Who's we?
I'll see you very soon, Lisbon.
Bye.
I don't know about this.
Oh, trust me.
You'll have fun.
"Trust me.
You'll have fun."
Was there ever
a more suspicious phase?
J.J., you have to live a little.
You spend your days
chasing paper clip thieves.
When do you ever get the chance
to nail a killer?
No, it's true.
I'm happy to help.
It's the performance aspect
that concerns me.
What performance aspect?
You go into a room.
If someone says anything to you
you say, "Ha ha ha",
or perhaps...
Ha ha ha.
Perhaps.
Good enough.
Would an accent help?
Keep it simple.
As you know, this, show
has faced a great deal of hardship
and tragedy the past few days.
But I can tell you
that it has only made us stronger.
Evening, Lisbon, you having fun yet?
There you are. Where have you been
and what's your plan?
I will tell you in one minute.
Oh, good evening,
and what an evening it is.
- Lisbon, you remember Mr. Dodge?
- Of course.
Agents, what are you doing here?
Ah, I've gotta tell you, Mr. Dodge
after watching all those rehearsals
we couldn't just stay away,
could we?
Okay, Warren, you're supposed
to go say something.
Yes, I know. I'm ready.
Finally, let me introduce
our esteemed producer
Warren Dodge, to tell you...
Who is that?
Oh, my goodness.
It's Berndt Hanover.
Mr. Hanover. Hi.
What a wonderful surprise.
Mr. Hanover, such an honor.
I'm...I'm Sylvia Clare.
We spoke on the phone.
Your trip was a good one, I hope?
Yes, it was very good.
Thank you, Ms. Clare.
- Sure.
- Excuse me. What's going on?
Warren? Why don't you come out
and talk to the lovely people?
Ms. Clare, I have come to address
my fellow investors.
Why don't I go and speak
to them now?
What?
Oh, terrific.
That is a great idea.
- Isn't it, Warren?
- Who are you, huh?
Wait. What are you doing?
He's not Berndt Hanover.
He's a fraud!
Warren! What is going on?
I don't know what game he's playing
but he's not Hanover.
Well, what are you saying?
Then who is he?
His name is J.J. LaRoche.
Mr. Dodge is correct.
It isn't Berndt Hanover.
Okay, I'm totally confused.
Ah, we faked it...the hat, the glasses
the cane, the coat.
- Et voila. Berndt Hanover.
- But why?
A test. You all believed it was him
and it was easy to make you believe it.
For about ten seconds,
until he said that I wasn't.
And then nobody believed it anymore
just like I don't believe anymore
that Berndt Hanover exists.
- What? Well, that's ridiculous.
- Is it?
Of course Berndt Hanover exists.
Then produce him.
You're a producer. Where is he?
Well... I just can't magically
make him appear.
Call him.
- Mr. Jane, I don't have his number on me.
- Hard to believe.
You know, it's at my office
and I will call him there,
when I'm...
- I have it. I'll call him.
- That's lucky.
- I'm calling him.
- Good idea.
- It's ringing.
- Excellent.
He might not answer.
He's a...he's a very busy man.
Of course.
Excuse me.
Your coat is playing
the "Fifth Symphony."
Gonna answer that,
Mr. Dodge?
Or should we call you mister...
Hanover?
Hello? Sorry. Mr. Dodge
can't come to the phone
right now, Sylvia.
He's a little busy getting arrested.
Hanover didn't come down
in the elevator
because Hanover
never even existed.
Dodge was playing the part
from the beginning.
He took off his disguise,
eluded the cameras
by coming down a fire escape.
Lisbon, he's all yours.
You're under arrest.
Tell me that wasn't fun.
I cannot tell you that,
but we are even, yes?
Yes.
I wanted the show to work.
I was willing to do anything.
- Even kill?
- W...
She surprised me.
"When I was changing
out of the Hanover costume"
"nobody was supposed to be
in the room at that time."
"Nobody."
"I told her that I put every penny
I had into the show"
"and that Hanover was necessary
to give our investors"
"a confidence
and peace of mind"
"and that once I had the money
I needed"
"I would make
Hanover disappear"
and that everything
would work out in the end.
But she said no.
"She wouldn't be
any part of it..."
"That she was going to
tell Sunderland"
"which of course meant
that everyone would find out"
"and... that would have ruined
everything."
Yeah. I didn't mean
for this to happen.
So what happened next?
I left by the fire escape.
No one saw me.
And then I went and got
in my car around the corner
and I drove up and introduced
myself to the police.
This was gonna be the hit show
that put me back on top.
Everyone would have benefited.
If only she hadn't
walked through that door.
I, I didn't have
nearly enough time with her.
And I so loved the person
that she was and respected her.
Thank you for giving her justice.
It means a lot.
I'm sorry.
Embarrassing.
I have to take this.
- Excuse me.
- Of course.
- Hello?
- "Patrick, it's Sheila from the hospital."
They're bringing him
out of the coma.
When?
You need to get over here.
Okay. Um... s... I...
He's conscious,
but keep an eye on him.
Hit that button,
and we'll be right in.
Okay, thank you, nurse.
You are one tough S.O.B.,
Jason Lennon.
You really are.
Where am I?
What happened?
You're in Sacramento.
You got shot.
- Do you remember that?
- Yes, I do.
Lorelei Martins.
Correct. Very good.
Good. Your mind is clear.
Now listen, I have a question
for you, Jason.
Look at me.
Look close.
You recognize me?
You ever seen me before?
No.
Are you sure?
It's important.
Yes.
I'm sure.
That's good to know.
Thanks.
Who are you?
I'm a friend.
Let's face facts, Jason.
If you recover and live
you'll spend life in prison for murder...
the plaything of monsters.
I just hope that if I'm
ever in your shoes
I have a friend close enough
to do this for me.
Wait.
Now don't be scared.
This'll be quick.
With very little pain.
It's okay.
It's all right.
I'm here for you.
I won't leave you.
Help! Nurse!
Nurse!
He's in V-fib.
- Get that crash cart over here.
- "Code blue, code blue in 116"
"Code blue in 116"
"Code blue, code blue in 116"
- "Code blue in 116"
- 300. Clear.
I'll get Mike.
- No response.
- Grace, get Mike...
What happened?
Patrick, I'm sorry.
His heart gave out.
Never said a word.